{
    "id": "da5c7459027e4d54b8905282d73d4451",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We are all waiting for the ——————— of the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "confirm",
                "confirmation",
                "confirmed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d1731175b4aa49b38a2d2c60920bfafb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though the boy isn’t very intelligent, he is very ————————",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "industry",
                "industrial",
                "industrious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7933715f3160415f8b9e95100983c237"
        },
        {
            "question": "The governor refused to accept the ————————- of the Chief Minister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "resign",
                "resignation",
                "resignment"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cf36379a434491cbc58c081ddf01907"
        },
        {
            "question": "The students are all very ———————– about the picnic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enthused",
                "enthusiasm",
                "enthusiastic"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4ce90dfad964d81ab8c0992edcf9e2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The committee’s proposal was not ——————- to the government.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accepted",
                "acceptable",
                "acceptance"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac102e715f324404bc0ce0714b2c1d45"
        },
        {
            "question": "India is a land of great cultural ———————-",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "diversion",
                "diversity",
                "diverse"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04220bd090ee44f58e349eded40124fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Failure is the stepping stone to ——————",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "success",
                "succession"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd381acf732942e5abaec5a5f7c23f87"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government gave him ———————- to go abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "permit",
                "permission"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5ecc274f8e1466197a360e39e5d733e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Film stars enjoy great ———————-",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "popular",
                "popularity",
                "population"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2fd28d579564891ac20269423bb4e9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must stop our ———————— on fossil fuels.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "depend",
                "depending",
                "dependence"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "55c3ce1f38dd4c089bcb15ec7cf8289a"
        }
    ]
}